reallusion.com 2006-10-20

# Reallusion 3d animation and text to speech software

|  | 

Privacy Policy

Reallusion.com realizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personal information. Personal information includes all of the information provided by the customers or collected by Reallusion.com. 

Reallusion.com collects information throughout http://www.Reallusion.com web site, including anonymous site statistics, domain names, and/or IP addresses. On specific pages, Reallusion.com gives users the option of providing names, addresses, phone numbers, fax numbers, email addresses, and other personal information. This information is gathered only with your knowledge and active permission and participation.

When you complete and submit a form requesting additional information, you will be asked for personal information in order to process your request. This information will be retained by Reallusion.com.

When you send us an email, we will retain the content of the email, your email address, and our response in order to handle any follow-up questions you may have. 

Reallusion.com has the highest regard for the privacy of its customers and other visitors to our web site. As a result, we safeguard the privacy of users of our online services with the same degree of care we protect our own information. 

In some instances, Reallusion.com may review personal information (e.g., IP address logs for file transfers), while in other cases we may use the information to generate anonymous statistics. Log file analysis helps us to monitor general trends in our site traffic so that we can determine how our web site can be more effective. 

We will also use personal information to identify you, communicate with you, help us respond to your questions, and understand which Reallusion.com products and services best meet your needs.

Under no circumstances will Reallusion.com sell personal information to any third party for any purpose. We may, however, share personal information with our business partners for the sole purpose of delivering products and services that you have requested and in order to communicate with you about Reallusion.com, its products and services. We may also release, to the minimum extent possible, specific personal information to comply with valid legal processes such as search warrants, or court orders. 

|
